yescourse.com 2018-09-04

# Privacy Policy

The privacy of your personal information is important to us. YesCourse Pty Ltd - ABN 61166713499 (YesCourse) may collect personal information through the websites available at the domains owned by YesCourse including but not limited to yescourse.com and all sub-domains (Site), or directly from you. YesCourse respects your right to privacy and this policy sets out how we collect and treat your personal information. Please read the following Privacy Policy carefully.

“Personal information” is information we hold which is identifiable as being about you. Personal information collected by us will only be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the Australian Privacy Principles.

## What personal information we collect

There are many aspects of the site which can be viewed without providing personal information, however, you may be required to submit personally identifiable information from time to time. This may include:

    names;  
    date of birth;  
    job titles;  
    contact information including addresses, email addresses, phone numbers, fax numbers, social media usernames etc;  
    demographic information;  
    information about goods and services you have ordered;  
    information from enquiries you have made;  
    information about your business or personal affairs;  
    communication between us;  
    credit card information;  
    other information relevant to promotions; and  
    any other information requested on this Site or otherwise required by us or provided by you.

We may contact you by a variety of measures to voluntarily respond to questionnaires, surveys or market research to seek your opinion and feedback. Providing this information is optional to you. We may receive personal information from third parties. If we do, it will be protected as set out in this Privacy Policy.

## Non-personally identifiable information

For each visitor to the site, we collect the following non-personally identifiable information, including but not limited to pages viewed while browsing the site, browser and operating systems, page access times and referring website address. This collected information is used solely internally for the purpose of gauging visitor traffic, trends and delivering personalized content to you while you are at the site.

## How we collect your personal information

We collect personal information from you in a variety of ways, including: when you interact with us electronically or in person; when you access our website; and when we provide our services to you.

## Use of your personal information

We may use your personal information to provide the YesCourse service to you and to provide you with information from us and our partners . We may use your personal information to better understand customer needs, improve our website and improve our service. We may use your personal information to respond to queries about our service and documents requests. We also use your personal information for marketing purposes, to improve our service and to notify you of opportunities that we think you might be interested in.

## Disclosure of personal information

We may share your information with organisations, agents, contractors and subcontractors that assist us to provide information, products and services to you (YesCourse Associates). Those organisations will receive only the information they need to help deliver the YesCourse service. By using the YesCourse website you consent to the disclosure of your information to YesCourse Associates. We take reasonable steps to ensure that these YesCourse Associates are bound by confidentiality and privacy obligations in relation to the protection of your personal information. We may also disclose information when it is required by law. We may disclose information to parties located outside of Australia. These locations may include, but are not limited to, the United States of America, the Philippines and India.

In addition to the above, your personal details may be made available to the academies that you enrol in as students, trainers, tutors and support staff. YesCourse and Academies also have access to information related your activities within their courses including but not restricted to if and when you have viewed course material, attempted assignments and any other interaction that you have with the Academy's facilities on the site.

## Security

We take reasonable steps to protect your personal information. However, we are not liable for any unauthorised access to this information. The transmission and exchange of information is carried out at your own risk. We take steps to safeguard against unauthorised disclosures of information, however we cannot assure you that personal information will not be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

## Cookies

As is very common for companies, we use cookies on our website. Cookies are very small files which a website uses to identify you when you come back to the site and to store details about your use of the site. Cookies are not malicious programs that access or damage your computer. We use cookies to improve the experience of people using our website. You have the option to accept or decline cookies. You can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies if you prefer. This may, however, prevent you from taking full advantage of the Site.

## Third party sites

Our site has links to other websites not owned or controlled by us. We are not responsible for these sites or the consequences of you going on to those sites.

Third parties may use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to collect or receive information from our website and elsewhere on the internet and use that information to provide measurement services and target ads. You have the option to opt-out of the collection and use of information for ad targeting, by visiting [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).

## Accessing your personal information

You have a right to access your personal information in accordance with the provisions of the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth). If you would like to do so, please contact us at privacy@yescourse.com and let us know. You may be required to put your request in writing for security reasons. We reserve the right to charge a fee for searching for, and providing access to, your information on a per request basis. We reserve the right to refuse to provide you with information that we hold about you, in certain circumstances set out in the Privacy Act.

If you believe that any information we hold on you is inaccurate, out of date, incomplete, irrelevant or misleading, please contact us at support@yescourse.com. We will respond to any request shortly after receiving it and will endeavour to promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

## Complaints

If you have any complaints about our privacy practices, please feel free to send in details of your complaints to "YesCourse Pty Ltd - 34 Auld Avenue, Eastwood, NSW 2000 Australia". We take complaints very seriously and will respond shortly after receiving written notice of your complaint.

## Changes

Please be aware that we may amend this Privacy Policy in the future with changes, additions and deletions, at our discretion. Your continued use of the Site following any amendments indicates that you accept the amendments. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are aware of any changes.
